Huh?
At first it looked like a woman standing there .. Yes, a woman!
What the hell was that?
You laughed now?
No, I haven't laughed.
Oh, it's a woman in front of us!
She turned out to be very clear, dark hair.
I shudder all over my body.
I saw her so clearly.
Did you hear the bang over there?
A really severe bang I heard.
It was a light ... a light ball ..
Now someone took hold of my West.
Then we are in Château de Veauce here in France and Wilma, you are there.
Yes, I'm with.
A medium, which hopefully will be a good tool for us so we can get this investigation further.
It is an exciting castle, very, very, old and they have these castles the ghost, Lucie that goes up there between two towers you can say.
Just.
And this is something that happened during the 80s, I think it was, so they caught a very strange picture of Lucie up there.
So we will focus on that.
It goes far back with this too, it was guards during the 15-1600s, who have seen her go there.
It will be interesting.
And it is big, partly it is the whole dungeon down there under us, where we should start I think.
Then we have this floor up here, here another investigator has been given a touch.
And you even see how this string moves, on the sweater.
Just.
We have seen a unique clip that has not been released.
You see how something is moved on your arm, and it is a string.
Of course, we are going in there.
It gets very interesting.
And then we have this time up, at the top between the two towers.
So it gets interesting.
We will run a lot of technology and equipment and then see if you Wilma can help us on the pile.
Get more about what's here.
What do you say, should we go down to the basement?
We start there.
Now we have gone down to this basement, it starts directly with a steep staircase and old objects.
We don't really know what has happened down here.
We will try to communicate and we will go into a special room.
There we will see if you can tuna in on something.
And so we see if we can get the instruments to react to it too.
It can be quite cool, because there is death here, it goes so far back in time all this.
But who is moving here?
We only know Lucie.
Yes, that is what is known here, but then there is certainly much more.
You two together will come up with something about the story, I'm sure.
Niclas hears a woman talk.
What did you hear?
It sounded like a woman talking.
Yes.
Before we came here, I knew a woman who shows that she was pregnant or that she had miscarriage.
And that she was very hurt about this.
So it may have any connection to it.
Because I also felt when we went here, that someone is waiting for us.
Someone who wants to get their voice heard tonight.
Should we go in there and see if we capture this?
Now we don't speak French.
But we try to communicate in English and Swedish of course.
I do so, if you are left here I put instruments further away, and we will see if the energies can come towards us.
I will post on each side of a beam there.
One is PRS.
Where we will get static or REM function.
And then PDA, Paranormal Direct Answer.
Red or green, answers questions.
So I put them a bit away.
And this will be like a motion Detector as well.
Now it lies there and pulsates and it lies and senses there.
Should we secure behind us?
I put an exercise detector there.
Now I got up on Ovilus ..
Together, smile now, what does that mean?
Now we come to you.
It's a big hole down there.
Oh!
Have you opened that door?
Wasn't it closed when we were here before?
Well ... if it has been closed then our surveillance camera took it.
That the door was closed before we can't look at the surveillance, that's something that obscures the camera
We have to check it.
Niclas hears a whistle
It sounded like someone whistled.
But, we must not go there.
Yes, he was there and felt on the door and said we must not go in there.
Test run your hand there so spring we see.
You can go here.
He said we couldn't go there.
It is still the energy that she is trying to play us a joke.
For now I see that she is sitting here and just keeps mocking when we are heading in there.
And like "blaming yourself".
There is such a difference because first she was welcoming and then when we came in here she shifted immediately.
And she wants to shovel us in there all the time.
Maybe stroll with surveillance?
Do we have someone with here?
There are such holes everywhere.
Is there water there?
Disturbance only on Niclas microphone
Sure damn there is water there.
Exactly, water is also an element.
Try pressing your hand over there then.
Grab my arm.
I feel a great cold when you said so, it comes from.
From where you stand against us.
Come out here!
Too bad we can't go in there ... But we must not do it, it's racially risk,
Close this door.
So it gets really cold ..
It sounded like something fell into the water.
We are not afraid of you.
You just get more curious to go in there.
Did it disappear?
Yes.
On the other side there.
Come out here, come to me.
And then it backs, it's just like "coming again, going through the door".
It's alluring all the time.
They should not get it.
Then they can sneak out here to us.
Exactly.
As I mentioned, the female energy, it feels like she has done her job now.
So that energy is gone.
So it was perhaps that she would bring us inward.
I think of Incubus, it's a woman ... no saccubus it is ...
Was it close properly?
What is it?
At first it looked like a woman standing there in the water ...
Yes, a woman standing there in the water!
I only saw the contours, this white you talked about.
She stood there in the water.
I got it confirmed, because she stood down there and looked up.
I just shudder my arms.
So unpleasant.
Yes, she just stood there.
I closed that now, if I closed something else for that was ....
I see you and then we got confirmed there.
Attract one in the water.
What does she want to do there?
Download one ..
what's your name?
Are your lucie?
I heard the water down there now, like it was dropping.
And then when you asked about names, I got up in my head, Felice or Felicia.
Though a French pronunciation.
I take Polterscript.
What I think is so interesting also is that this energy really turns out, manifests itself.
So cool that you see it.
You saw it first, this white.
But not as you described it.
I saw it more like a square type, like it was something white.
But it's unpleasant ..
Tony feels something on his cheek
I do not come up with what it is called, but like we mock type ..
What happens now?
It's a spider network here ...
There is a lot of spider web on you here.
Now this cold comes when you talk about it.
Imagine a nail that pulls towards the beard and that pulls down here to the chin and stays there.
As soon as you start talking about it, I feel this cold.
Open this door.
If you want us in there, open the door.
What the hell was that?
I don't usually back back, but that was ...
I hope we have it on the camera.
Did you film here?
Yes.
Then we can analyze this, if it was a bat that looked over the edge.
Or waved across the edge.
What we see now in retrospect is a bat flying towards the door and turns
Just when you say it, when you look there.
Can you do it again?
Open the door.
I feel such a strange energy behind it.
It is not an energy from a person I know, but there is more someone who crawl like this.
There is something or something else, something that has not belonged to a human being.
Very strange, I haven't encountered it so much before.
You haven't encountered that example.
Yes, that is something new as well.
This is the first time, it went so fast so I don't know.
I want to put logic on it first, if it was a bat that showed up there.
But that damn timing.
It is terrible.
It like an old gray hand that was on the way ....
We can't place so much emphasis on it either, that's what we discovered and that's what we knew and what we think we saw, but the analysis will see it.
Yes exactly.
Come out here.
Now it starts to burn here.
Damn, it's like ...
Do we have something here?
It is such a strong lamp so it is difficult to see.
Damn, it's like a nail here.
So unpleasant.
If there is someone down there ...
show yourself.
But I think we let this be now.
We have a camera here, so the doors open these doors so Lennie shouts to us right away.
Okay, are you following us?
This is an interesting room, check out all the wine bottles around here.
I think they said there are over 3000 wine bottles here.
Here it would be fun if something was thrown.
That it moves very quickly and it is like she does not want or can get any communication.
Without just that she can make us see her fast.
I put out the motion detector at about the height where the cork machine is, if someone comes in.
If she moves fast, hopefully this will take it.
But it would have been interesting if that had also picked it up.
Now I went into it.
But I think, because you Wilma get to you something that could show up in surveillance, so I call Lennie so he is in control of it.
Lennie, have some control when now for Wilma feel that the light phenomenon may come or that you can possibly see something.
So, in that case, call us on the radio.
Yes.
We must also keep in mind that Lennie is sitting up there.
It can slap up there, we have not added any instrument there just because it should not be difficult to sit there.
He sits there in the dark, he has a surveillance system.
But if it starts to move and bang there, then he calls to us so we have to go up there.
For this is a little unexplored area, you come here with your knowledge, you give us some theories on what it can be and what you feel.
We see things.
We experience crazy things.
And it is not very much that has happened here, but we go through everything, so we go to the active areas later.
Do we have someone here who could throw something?
Throw a wine bottle.
I walk around a bit and see if we catch something.
If the woman jumping around is here ...
That was a man's voice, did you hear that?
I heard a man who said something.
The voice is caught, but weak
I feel like ...
It is, sorry for being departed, but it is Johnny.
It came through a name.
Is Johnny here?
It doesn't sound like it's SP's usual French name.
But then we should keep that in mind that those who own it now are from England.
I'm not double.
I'm modern.
Just what I was talking about.
I'm not double but I'm modern, Johnny.
And it's women's voice on this ...
Imagine what I said there.
Johnny may have to do with them, modern time.
And like I'm not a double copy of anything, I'm real.
Everything is so cool, which comes through.
And I feel very small suddenly.
I feel almost shrunk, like my energy is depressed.
Like I can't get any kind of contact, like someone holding my mouth on me.
A little so I feel.
Does it feel like you are getting medially blocked?
Yes exactly.
And that you take my identity and just squeeze it down, like snapping together a paper.
So I feel all the time.
But if you back a little, down there.
Change place with her Tony.
If you back down more towards that window there.
See if you know if it is stronger there, where Tony stood.
Now it starts in my face.
As a spider web.
But not like nails?
No, it was like someone pulled a string type, which got stuck in the beard.
Here I feel that it is easier because here I come back and collect impressions again.
But as I approach where you stand, then it is like I get depressed.
It's here, it's like a magnet, here it stops me.
Here it is like I get small again.
It is the impressions that he shows me, so the question is whether it can be connection ...
Imagine what happened to him who owns this.
The dog that came at night ..
Yes exactly.
He realized that this is a ghost dog.
And it is quite interesting when he gets this, I can take the whole story ..
The owner lies and wakes up in the morning, he sees that a dog will go by the bed.
And he realizes that we have no dog, we have no animals here, everything is locked.
Then he thinks he should stretch his hand, then he knows how the hand hits the head of the dog, then the dog jumps up also
And lay next to him and lay there for a while.
He just lay there completely still and did nothing, then the dog jumped down, went and disappeared.
Now it says dog.
And there are tracks in the stone up there, paw prints.
Just.
It feels like we are no longer coming right here.
Should we move one floor up?
We go to Lucie's.
!
Huh?
It's a woman in front of us, she turned out to be very clear.
Dark hair.
So, it was a woman who laughed.
She hovered, with dark hair.
Directly in front of.
I shudder all over my body.
I shudder on the whole ....
I saw her so clearly.
So very clear.
We must have caught this.
We have caught it on that microphone if Johan is there.
It was clearly a woman who laughed.
And she really hovered like this.
Like she hovered by.
Show you again.
That laugh.
Should we follow in directly?
You can do that.
Lucie?
If you're here ...
can you show yourself?
I get a pressure over my chest, almost like anxiety on.
I also felt that when I walked in that corridor, where you have heard the dog.
And that grief comes along.
It is here that they have photographed, Nicke.
Yes.
In the 80s sometime, what thinks this is the ghost then.
I will put this here.
And direct it straight up to the beam.
So it will be the whole area, so we back a little.
Yes, I took it out.
An old honest flux, I put it down too.
So we back.
You don't have to be afraid of us.
We're just here to talk to you.
I put down another flux.
I get a lot of communication here and I get direct contact with this woman.
I think it's Lucie.
She shows me how she cries and then how she has to be quiet, like someone holding her mouth.
She has a lot of anxiety and shows such emotions.
And that she backs up a little because she has learned that you should not talk, or that she was not allowed to talk when she lived.
We are down here now, we have all the conditions.
If Wilma sits there Tony, you sit there first.
I place some instruments here, I will post a flux here on the table.
Or no, we take flux in front of you.
Because that is an old magic table you used here.
Perfect.
This is where he sat.
Exactly, I can do a little reconstruction.
Because we will not be able to show it, we got to see a unique clip.
He had some string here.
And you see something that does so and he reacts immediately.
And it's pretty interesting.
If you sit down there.
I know a man directly standing close to you and moving around you.
Because I feel a cold between us, clearly.
Here it is warmer, then here it gets icy.
So it's around you.
Okay, you may touch me.
Lift up my sweater.
Go to the blue light on the table there.
I feel that the man is there and he tells me that you should respect the fine room.
When we go in here we will go in with respect and we will almost ask for permission before
We sit down or before we touch things.
So it is very important to him that we respect the room.
For this room is classified as very nice for them.
For him.
It's a man we have?
Yes, it's a man.
This man, can you go to one of our things we have here?
That iron stick on the table, there is a lot that is not usually here.
Should I take the phone again and test some French phrases?
Do it, then we also see if we get a reaction.
I ask if they have touched a person sitting on this chair.
What happened there?
There were double votes.
It was an echo, did you hear that?
No light phenomenon was caught on the surveillance
Why do I see them with my own eyes?
I've never been able to see it.
Touch me.
Say, touch any of us.
Before you do it, wait ...
I put it on the Sean table here.
Touch any of us.
Hard thumps in the room
Did you hear?
A bang.
It was behind Johan somewhere.
Niclas, I think you and I should change places.
Because I always hear that the woman should sit on the couch.
Okay.
You should not sit there.
I ask if it wants us to leave the castle.
We can test, we know a little bit, we may have a little name.
We can see if we can interpret anything.
I go and pick up one.
If we are in the finroom then there should be no toys here.
So I put this on the couch.
So we'll see.
So it's the same thing, if something comes close to this ...
It should definitely not be there.
Throw that teddy if you want.
Now I start Spiritbox.
Voice of a man comes through
What was that?
There are lots of votes, as you say there are many here.
As soon as you started it there I see lots.
Everyone comes here.
Voice of a woman comes through
Stir my arm here now.
Or my sweater.
It's like they are sitting at the table.
Just.
Woman.
It's like they have a conference or something.
No.
But it confirms what you say that there is a lot of energies in here.
And when we open this noise, that's when it usually starts because then they realize that we hear them.
This was interesting, sound at each chair.
No touch.
Did he sit later or?
Insect flying past
Ask if they sit at this table, in French.
Niclas batteries in the mosquito die, Niclas tests with PMB behind Tony while we wait for new batteries, to see if there is anyone behind him
Immediately.
I start with PMB here.
Straight into that chair.
Is it the same?
Is it the one who comes up and visits them sometimes or is it two?
It got colder here.
But I think it's so, it's an energy on the bottom floor.
I don't think it goes up here.
It is a woman, it is a woman who is very strong down there.
We see her, we hear her.
If I sit down here ..
Should we sit down and just listen in a little?
Duns and steps are heard in the building
I see it as it is one and the same time or event that is played.
I see it as this is a nice dinner you have, with important people.
Sitting around this table.
And here there is a man of higher .. There may be any king or a prince.
He should sign something.
Then it is mixed with men and women sitting around here.
I see how he writes on something and that you bowl in very nice glass.
This goes as in a loop all the time, the same sequence all the time, as in a movie.
It sounds like it's a big event.
Yes and that may be why I do not feel seen, because they are here and now in this.
They do not see or do not care that something else is happening around.
Can you move aside again?
When you talked, I thought I saw a light passing there, right in front of you Niclas.
That's what I say, there are so many cool things happening here.
Imagine the light phenomenon, you see a woman floating.
I see a woman standing in the water looking up.
We hear her, twice.
Then the touch has been documented, so there is something that moves here.
But I don't understand why we'll see right now?
These light phenomena.
We have not experienced this before, that we see.
No I know.
I'll check if there was any kind of reflection, but I don't think they.
We take one with communication, which talks a little.
Polterscript.
It will throw out words.
We may be able to find out what they wrote on.
Find out what they wrote on yes ...
There is something about what you were talking about.
Does anyone have happened in connection with the fact that you wrote on the paper?
Something fate around ...
Is there anything special about that paper?
About the castle?
Something unresolved that you want to convey and tell us about?
Six.
How many chairs are there?
Eight..
Lennie, is in control of the door now.
Now Lennie is sitting out there listening.
It said door, silence and door.
There may be doors here too.
Can you close them the doors?
Close that door in front of us.
I tested that chair, the one, the ..
Everyone has been votes on and there are six chairs.
It's awesome.
And that I knew that there are important people sitting here.
They talk about something important and these people have power over something.
Tony, should we make us sweep through the last two?
There are two more rooms ..
Wait, we go up and go a little neighbor, move us a bit.
Just.
We let Wilma interpret and we bring some communication.
Statical!
Directly when we leave, things went here.
REM went on and static field swept around it.
Tony hears a voice of a woman in the room
Now I heard someone here who said ... but it was a woman.
Did you say anything Lennie?
He is very far away.
I know.
It was here type ...
Nothing on Polterscript either.
It feels calm.
It is interesting that you get it, but it may not be as strong as the other there.
We will take the next one too.
Here it is much more life and movement.
Here you have done something social, here is The Play Room or what to say.
This is where you really hang out and bowls.
And you might have some dance or activity here.
So here there is a lot of movement around me and very happy energies.
So it is completely different if you compare with the room where we were before.
Something left here?
It's like going in here when you celebrate something, if you have won something, then you go in here and celebrate.
Okay.
If I want to say what I think has been here, I think they have had a large pool table here.
The men have been in here and done things as well.
It's not that far from what you say.
There are matches, you celebrate something.
It's awesome.
There is a lot of memory energies I think.
There is nothing on communication.
It's good that you get what you say, but it doesn't feel like a very active room.
We have a room left.
No, we have two rooms left.
Here it is like I am being retracted, like coming in, came in.
Here I can feel an energy, not a memory but here someone is pulling us in.
Like a circus director ...
A throw -in?
Yes exactly.
Anyone here and want to talk to us?
That's it too, we're here now, we got access to this castle, to document Lucie and all of them here.
But we also had the opportunity to go down into the basement, we have been given the opportunity to go on all floors.
And I can say it's pretty quiet here.
But we have our ghost up there.
And it's interesting, because we've got a completely different thing
And it would be really interesting to hand it over to him later.
And tell us about what we have got down in the basement.
So if more paranormal investigators are to be here, then go down into the basement.
This is where the strongest is.
Because here it also feels no discomfort.
Quite pleasant, calm on the machines.
It's as you say, come in here.
The energies are just around here and are as nice as possible.
Really, exactly so.
It feels like the female energies are dominant tonight, that's what we have encountered for the most part.
If there is something left here ...
Can you move something?
Talk to us?
We have a bar here.
Can you do something with the glasses in here?
I also get to me that it may have any kind of strip club or a brothel.
Also linked to this abuse that I felt when I stepped in here.
It is that, this happened and it became a scandal.
That you were ashamed of this or that you tried to silence it.
I feel that in the energy, that you don't talk much about it.
Then it was really something that you silenced, because it was an important man who gave up on a woman.
And they didn't want to impair his reputation.
I think, we are in a castle, take that power.
And it also goes together with what I knew first, I think it was down in the basement, when I saw tape over my mouth.
That you become silent.
It was certainly then that the women were silenced, they would be silent.
So as not to impair men's status.
Just look at how the castle is designed here, soldiers and things were on the outside, in wooden places behind a wall.
The horses were at the far end of the yard and had their own stables, certainly heat ...
Now I saw it again ....
I saw it again, a ball of light or ...
Now someone took hold of my West.
Pulled behind it or?
I backed back, I thought I got stuck in something first.
What we can see is that Mel Meter on the right side of Nicla's chest goes up as it is stuck.
It went like a bow like that.
Against me?
Should we go out to the yard?
And try to look up at Lucie Tower?
And this dungeon.
If we see something.
Something light phenomenon or something moving in the window.
Because it has also been a guard who went down the stairs, who went up to a person's car and knocks on it
And the person gets completely dear, then a soldier from a long time ago goes back up the stairs and disappears.
We stand out here, in this history, we have the stable behind.
And we must not go into this building huh?
It is because of racial risk.
You see how the roofs have collapsed.
We were out here earlier today, you and Lennie would go up to the tower with the owner.
Then there will be a stone from the roof and we call for Lennie move on you!
And then, right next to him ...
And it happened over there.
Right where they have seen this soldier walking up and down.
It was really like you are not going to the tower.
It could have come stone over there and it is roof tiles that release.
This is very interesting.
And up here is Lucie Tower.
And up there in the hallway there we were watching.
And there in the dungeon she passed away.
We hear something going in the gravel
There was something that went there.
Stand still..
Someone went here.
Up there came the stone.
Was hit Lennie in the head.
It feels like someone is looking at us in that window.
The second window there.
That someone is just standing there looking at us.
It's not something I see but I just feel it.
Can you throw something if you're out here with us now?
It was above that window that it fell?
From the stupid there.
Being able to investigate a castle is always special.
And gaining access to this magical castle Château de Veauce in France is few to be found.
Who is the woman moving to the bottom floor that Niclas sees in the water?
Is it the same woman laughing and who Wilma senses?
Yes, a woman standing there in the water!
I only saw the contours, this white you talked about.
She stood there in the water.
Everything we experience is not paranormal, but the reactions can initially be so.
For example, we really thought we saw a shadow, until we realize that it is a bat that makes the shade down in the basement.
Then we can analyze this.
If it was a bat that looked over the edge.
In the remaining parts of the castle, it was difficult to communicate with what many have known.
We really tried to get a glimpse of castle the ghost Lucie who wanders between the two towers, but despite attempts to document her in several ways, she did not want to prove to us this time.